Two wrongs don't make a right.
The pen is mightier than the sword.
When in Rome, do as the Romans.
The squeaky wheel gets the grease.
People who live in glass houses should not throw stones.
Birds of a feather flock together.
Keep your friends close and your enemies closer.
There's no such thing as a free lunch.
The early bird catches the worm.
Never look a gift horse in the mouth.
You can't make an omelet without breaking a few eggs.
God helps those who help themselves.
Cleanliness is next to godliness.
If it ain't broke, don't fix it.
If you can't beat them, join them.
Necessity is the mother of invention.
A penny saved is a penny earned.
You can't judge a book by its cover.
Don't put all your eggs in one basket.
The grass is always greener on the other side.
Do unto others as you would have them do unto you.
A chain is only as strong as its weakest link.
Absence makes the heart grow fonder.
You can lead a horse to water, but you can't make him drink.
If you want something done right, you have to do it yourself.
Two wrongs don't make a right.
The pen is mightier than the sword.
When in Rome, do as the Romans.
The squeaky wheel gets the grease.
People who live in glass houses should not throw stones.
Birds of a feather flock together.
Keep your friends close and your enemies closer.
There's no such thing as a free lunch.
The early bird catches the worm.
Never look a gift horse in the mouth.
You can't make an omelet without breaking a few eggs.
God helps those who help themselves.
Cleanliness is next to godliness.
If it ain't broke, don't fix it.
If you can't beat them, join them.
Necessity is the mother of invention.
A penny saved is a penny earned.
You can't judge a book by its cover.
Don't put all your eggs in one basket.
The grass is always greener on the other side.
Do unto others as you would have them do unto you.
A chain is only as strong as its weakest link.
Absence makes the heart grow fonder.
You can lead a horse to water, but you can't make him drink.
If you want something done right, you have to do it yourself.
A dog is a man's best friend.
A fool and his money are soon parted.
A journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step.
A leopard cannot change its spots.
A little knowledge is a dangerous thing.
It's better to have loved and lost than never to have loved at all.
It's no use crying over spilt milk.
Laugh and the world laughs with you, weep and you weep alone.
March comes in like a lion, and goes out like a lamb.
Absence makes the heart grow fonder.
Actions speak louder than words.
Don't bite off more than you can chew.
Don't look a gift horse in the mouth.
Don't put all your eggs in one basket.
A foold and his money are soon parted.
The grass is always greener on the other side of the fence.
Imitation is the sincerest form of flattery.
Lightning never strikes twice in the same place.
A man is known by the company he keeps.
One man's gravy is another man's poison.
One swallow does not a summer make.
The proof of the pudding is in the eating.
The road to hell is paved with good intentions.
The spirit is willing, but the flesh is weak.
